

# Jaewon Lee

ROBOTICS · MULTI-ROBOT · SLAN

25, Galmaejungang-ro, Guri-si, Gyeonggi-do, 11902, Rep. of KOREA

 $\ \square$  (+82) 10-9114-2756 |  $\ \blacksquare$  ashcircle@kw.ac.kr |  $\ \blacksquare$  lee-jaewon.github.io |  $\ \boxdot$  Lee-JaeWon

"Passion is the genesis of genius."

## Summary.

This is Jaewon Lee, who wants to be a Robotics researcher and engineer. I am interested in Robotics, SLAM, Multi-Robot System. I think Robotics can help the development of the world a lot. I want to study a lot and approach the world.

## Research Interests

**SLAM** Multi-Robot, Descriptor

**Novel View Synthesis** 3D Scene Representation, Sensor-Fused Representation

## Education

## Yonsei University @CILAB

Seoul, S.Korea

COMBINED M.S. & Ph.D. IN ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING (ADVISOR: PROF. EUNTAI KIM)

Mar. 2024(Expected) -

• Research on Robotics

#### **KwangWoon University**

Seoul, S.Kore

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024

- GPA: 4.13/4.50, Major GPA: 4.29/4.50
- Club: BARAM Robotics (Robotics Academic Group) [2022 Vice President], Mar.2020-Feb.2024

# Work Experience\_

## Yonsei Univ @CILAB

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor: PROF. Euntai Kim)

Jul. 2023 - Present

- I Participated in ICCV 2023 SLAM Challenge
- I studied 3D Scene Representation

#### **ROBOMATION**

Seoul, S.Korea

R&D INTERN

Jun. 2022 - Aug. 2022

- I developed an automation system for soccer games using multi-robot.
- I developed multi-robot coordination and pose system using Aruco Marker.

## KwangWoon Univ @Robotics A.I. LAB.

Seoul, S.Korea

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor : PROF. Junghyun Oh)

Jan. 2022 - Jun. 2022

- I studied visual SLAM and visual odometry
- I studied Multi-Robot system and implemented Multi-Robot exploration

#### Honors & Awards

#### Awards

2023.12	2023 Hanium ICT Mentoring Competition, Silver Award	Ministry of Science and ICT. IITP. FKii
	ICCV 2023 SI AM Challenge	ana ret, irri, ritir

2023.10 Fourth place in LiDAR-Inertial Track - Taeyoung Kim, <u>Jaewon Lee</u>, Beomsoo Kim, Euntai Kim

2023.06 **Undergraduate Paper Award**, Paper - Autonomous multi robot parking system

1CROS 2023

2022.10 **Dean's list**, for Academic Excellence

Kwangwoon Univ.

#### **HONORS**

2022.10 Full Tuition Scholarship, for the first place in last semester

Kwangwoon Univ.

## **Publication**

#### DOMESTIC CONFERENCE

"Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System",

Jaewon Lee, Hyosuk Joo, Chung-gil Ahn, Hyedo Kim, Junghyun Oh - [Paper]

ICROS 2023

## Skills\_

**Programming** C++/C, Python, MATLAB **DevOps** ROS/ROS2, Docker, Git

**Framework** PyTorch, Tensorflow, Keras, Unity

## **Extracurricular Activity**

#### Technical Blog - lee-jaewon.github.io

Personal Tech Blog

WRITER

Jul. 2021 - Present

- I have been writing posts about the paper review, development, the study of Interests.
- · To study through writing and sharing.
- The blog is available at [here].

#### **Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System**

Kwangwoon Univ.

CAPSTONE DESIGN

Jan.2023 - Jun.2023

- · Implement a multi-robot system and implement various technologies necessary for mobile robots.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

#### 2022 Open Source Contribution Academy

Ministry of Science and ICT, NIPA

MENTEE

Jul. 2022 - Oct. 2022

• I contributed to translating PyTorch Hub English documents into Korean at the PyTorch Korean User's Group.

#### **Multi Robot Collision Avoidance with Velocity Obstacle**

BARAM Robotic

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2022 - Nov.2022

- $\bullet \ \ {\sf I} \ {\sf implemented} \ {\sf collision} \ {\sf avoidance} \ {\sf with} \ {\sf Velocity} \ {\sf Obstacle} \ {\sf using} \ {\sf multi-robot}.$
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

## **Autonomous Driving Simulation with Reinforcement Learning**

BARAM Robotic

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2021 - Nov.2021

- I implemented an Autonomous-driving system through DQN algorithm for the high-way situation.
- I implemented a simulator with Unity. And I managed the reward using Laser Sensor.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

#### Frontier Based Multi-Robot Exploration

BARAM Robotic

PERSONAL PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- I implemented ROS-based multi-robot frontier exploration.
- I implemented a multi-robot SLAM system using open sources.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

## **House Interior Classifier and Automatic Recommendation**

022 Deen Learning Lecture

DEEP-LEARNING PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- I implemented House Interior Classifier using Inception-Resnet-V2 in Keras.
- · I implemented a system that can automatically search on the actual shopping site with the classified result.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].